<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Utf-8"?>
<!--
    studente: clara tateyama fabbri
    matricola: 560405
    corso: codifica di testi 19-20
-->
<!DOCTYPE TEI SYSTEM "tei_all.dtd">
<TEI>
<teiHeader xml:lang="it">
 <fileDesc>
 <titleStmt>
 <title>Alice Mare</title>
<respStmt>
<resp>Conversione TEI P5 a cura di</resp>
<name>Clara Tateyama Fabbri</name>
</respStmt>
</titleStmt>
<publicationStmt>
   <publisher>Università di Pisa</publisher>
    <pubPlace>Pisa</pubPlace>
     <date>2020-10-21</date>
</publicationStmt>
<sourceDesc>
<bibl>
   <title>ALice Mare</title>
   <author>Miwashiba</author>
   <genre>Supernatural</genre>
   <type>Light Novel</type>
<publisher>
  <ref target="https://www.amazon.it"></ref>
</publisher>
   <date>2015-01-27</date>
  <price>1200</price>
</bibl>
</sourceDesc>
</fileDesc>
</teiHeader>
  <text xml:lang="en">
          <front>
            <titlePage>
                <docAuthor>Meteor Hoshizora</docAuthor>
                <docTitle>
                <titlePart type="main"></titlePart>
                </docTitle>
                <docEdition>1st edition</docEdition>
                <docImprint>
                    <pubPlace>Japan</pubPlace>
                    <publisher><ref target="https://www.amazon.it"></ref></publisher>
                    <date>2015-01-27</date>
                </docImprint>
            </titlePage>
        </front>
  <body>
    <head>Prologue</head>
      <div n="1">
        <p>The ant told me that the frog is bad. 
        The frog told me that the cat is bad. 
        The cat told me, <q>"No, the rabbit's the worst of all!"</q>
        So I... </p>

        <p>...My ears rang. Yet I could also hear it as a voice, trying to tell me something.
        Slumping down in the chair, I looked up. The ceiling began to warp into whiteness. 
        Wanting to check the time, I looked to where the clock should have been, but the numbers were black blots, squirming around like bugs; it wouldn't tell me anything useful.
        I knew this scene well. I could still never forget that day.
        <q>"...I <hi rend="italic">will</hi>end this,"</q>I muttered to no one in particular, shutting my eyes.
        There was no end in sight to the ringing. The voice seemed to get increasingly louder.</p>

        <p><q>"You want to be XXXXed? Then you just need to XXXX."</q>
        <q>"What should I XXXX?"</q>
        <q>"Let's see now... You should XXXX bad people. Then you'll be XXXXed, too."</q></p>

        <p>That was what the cat told me. ...No, actually, I couldn't quite remember if it was the cat who said it. 
        But I always wanted someone to XXXX me. It had been the only thing on my mind for a long time. 
        That's why I was observing the children at the facility and continuing to research - in hopes of finding an answer. 
        <q>"Ah, my head hurts..."</q>
        I tried to lift myself up and head for the bed. But instead, I powerlessly fell onto the desk. 
        I tried several times, but the worsening ringing in my ears and headache sapped my will. 
        <q>"...Oh well,"</q> I mumbled, and lay my head down on the desk.</p>

        <p>As I drifted off, amid the clamor of metallic sounds, I felt like I heard her voice.</p>
      </div>

    <head>Chapter 1:Good Night</head>
      <div n="2">
        <p>The long, white hallway went on. Every step echoed for long after I took it. 
        As this went on unchanging for a while, I felt indescribable anxiety and helplessness. The place I was in earlier, I saw people who looked like workers here and there, but now there were absolutely no signs of life. The total silence only added to my unease. 
        This town, situated next to a large forest, was a bustling place with lots of people. 
        Fairly large, albeit not enough to be called a city. Compared to the forest, where many families lived modest, meager lives, everyone here lived much more bountifully. 
        Now I was walking down the hallways of a large hospital built in the center of that town. 
        Last night, my friend who worked here as a doctor gave me a call:<q>"I've got a kid here at the hospital I want you to inspect."</q>
        <q>"Hey! Long time no see."</q> 
        With a lively shout, someone grabbed my shoulder from behind. 
        I turned around to a man in a white coat with a good-natured, freckled face topped with chestnut hair. 

        <q>"Glad I got the idea to come looking for you. ...So you got lost again, huh?"</q>, asked Cliff - my only friend - with a little smile. 

        <q>"...I guess I'm just not good at remembering places or directions. Ever since I started living there, I've only come to town for... just grocery shopping, I suppose."</q>

        <q>"Sure, but you've been living here for way longer, so... Well, yeah, you've gotten lost a lot of places ever since we met in college..."</q> Cliff's forehead wrinkled, and he knit his brows. 

        <q>"...Anyway, I still can't get over how you decided to buy that place and live there. There's always been weird rumors about it. You know? Like it being a mental hospital, or a place for human experimentation... I heard it all." </q>

        <q>"I have you to thank for that. And yes, it's an odd place. No windows, and one of the rooms does lend itself to those kinds of stories. But I have to say I like it, because people's reluctance to come near means it's quiet."</q>

        <q>"When you get right down to it, it's my fault, huh. ...So, what of that room, anyway? You mean the one on the second floor, down the left hall?"</q>, Cliff asked me, showing a bit of hesitation. 

        <q>"I didn't even want to so much as clean it up, so I just left it as it was and locked the door."</q>
        </p>
      </div>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
